The second map of Delta Treasure Month, Buck Stone is here. The reward this time is different from the dam.
And the secret is top secret, the treasure chests opened in different difficulties are the same. OK,
The following brings the specific locations of all treasures from Buck Stones 1 to 12,
You can choose the progress bar to watch in real time. First,
The location of Treasure Map No. 1 is on the right side of the second floor balcony of the house at the bottom of Blues Mountain City;
Treasure Map No. 2 is in the shed in front of the arch in Asara Camp;
Treasure map No. 3 is under the stone bench in the aisle leading to the bag drop truck in Cherry Town;
Treasure Map No. 4 is behind the wooden box on the far left edge next to Operation Broken Wings.
Treasure map No. 5 is located next to the tent in the middle of Baksh Bazaar.
Treasure map No. 6 is located next to the abandoned yellow car in the train carriage on the far right side of the map.
Treasure map No. 7 is in the pool connection center of the cistern area on the right side of the Tower of Babel.
Treasure Map No. 8 is located under the long table in the rest area on the second floor of the Tower of Babel.
Treasure map No. 9 is under the pipe board next to the computer room on the first floor of the museum.
Treasure map No. 10 is located under the toilet door of Baksh Fishing Ground.
Treasure map No. 11 is on the roof of the small house between Blues Mountain Town and the camp. Finally,
Treasure map No. 12 is in the corner of the sofa area next to the flight box on the top of the Tower of Babel.